Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman papers, 1942-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical 1957-2006
  - Organization/Subject 1967-2006
    - Miscellaneous 1960-1967
      - Michigan Partnership for New Education 1992 (Box 207)
      - Community Foundation for Southeastern Michigan (Box 207)
      - AAT Itineraries 1990 (Box 207)
      - Wolverine Land Company (Box 207)
      - Courtauld Institute of Art (Box 207)
      - Columbia University (pledge) (Box 207)
      - Greater Hermitage Assessment Committee 1998-1999 (Box 208)
      - Bound Collection of Articles
        - 1988 Macy's/Federated (Box 208)
        - 1986-1987 Pulitzer Publishing Company (Box 208)
        - 1986-1988 Wanamaker's (Box 208)
        - 1988-1989 Woodies/Morgan/Drexel (Box 208)
      - Senate Subcommittee on Education (statement of AAT) 1993 (Box 208)
- Personal 1950-2005
  - Biographical / Personal
    The bulk of the Personal series consists of correspondence received from friends and business associates between 1964 and 2001. Included in the correspondence are personal messages of support after his 2001 conviction and testimonial letters sent to the court prior to his sentencing. Note that some business correspondence is included in the personal correspondence files. This series also includes a small amount of biographical information, in the form of summaries prepared for publications, such as Who's Who; plaques, awards, and certificates, including honorary degrees; and records of club memberships.
    - Biographical Summaries Prepared for Various Who's Who Publications (Box 209)
    - Clubs, Correspondence and Membership Cards, 2 folders (Box 209)
    - A. Alfred Taubman Tribute to WWJ Radio on Its 70th Anniversary 1990, audiocassette (Box 209)
    - A. Alfred Taubman Personal Bank Book 1950-1952 (Box 209)
    - A. Alfred Taubman College of Architecture and Urban Planning dedication 1999 (Box 209)
    - American Institute of Architects Honorary Membership 1999 (Box 209)
  - Speeches
    - Anton, Tom, memorial service, July 19 2006, .ZIP file
    - Council of Michigan Foundations Board of Trustees, June 7 1990, .ZIP file
    - Detroit Chamber of Commerce 1990 (Box 210)
    - Fisher, Max M., eulogy and opening remarks at meeting for the United Jewish Communities Campaign 2005, .ZIP file
    - Frank Lloyd Wright Conference opening remarks, undated, .ZIP file
    - Harvard Business School 1984 (Box 210)
    - Harvard Business School Club of Detroit 1983 (Box 210)
    - Jewish Community Center 1997 (Box 210)
    - Lawrence Institute of Technology 1985 (Box 210)
    - Michigan Partnership for New Education Board Meeting 1991-1993, 3 folders (Box 210)
    - Northern Michigan University Commencement Address 1995 (Box 210)
    - Russian Trip News Releases and Related Material 1985 (Box 210)
    - United Foundation 1983 (Box 210)
    - University of Chicago Graduate School of Business 1985, 2 folders (Box 210)
    - University of Michigan, "America's Institutions," 1985 (Box 210)
    - University of Michigan Medical School commencement address, "Continuing the Michigan Tradition," 1984, .ZIP file
    - University of Michigan-Urban Land Institute Real Estate Forum November 6, 2003, .ZIP file
    - Urban Land Institute [ULI], 50th anniversary meeting 1986, .ZIP file
  - Articles about A. Alfred Taubman
    - Art & Antiques "Top 100 Collectors in America," 1985-1986 (Box 210)
    - Avenue Magazine, April 2007, .ZIP file
    - Business Week Handouts, 1971 (Box 210)
    - Business Week"Shopping centers grow into shopping cities," September 4, 1971, .ZIP file
    - CBS News"For Billionaire There's Life After Jail," April 15, 2007, .ZIP file
    - Corporate Detroit, "Details, Details, the Master Emphasizes," April 1993, .ZIP file
    - Donald Bred Articles 1987 (Box 210)
    - DBusiness, "A. Alfred Taubman Saves a Residential Gem" and "Taubman, Take Two," 2011, .ZIP file
    - Detroit Free Press"Carol Cain hears leaders' practical wishes for 2011" January 2, 2011, .ZIP file
    - Detroit Free Press Magazine, "Al Taubman: The private man becomes a public person," August 7, 1983, .ZIP file
    - Detroit Monthly, "He's Beyond Rich," 1990, .ZIP file (Box 210)
    - Detroit News"1983 Business Celebrities," 1983 (Box 210)
    - Detroit News, "Taubman still king of shopping malls," June 25, 2009, .ZIP file
    - Forbes 400 (Box 211)
      - 1982-1987, 2 folders (Box 211)
    - Forbes 400 and World's Billionaires
      - 1988-1993, 3 folders (Box 211)
    - Forbes 400, 2001-2003 (Box 211)
    - Fortune (cover image), April 21, 1980, .JPG file
    - Fortune, The Billionaires (Box 212)
      - 1987-1992, 2 folders (Box 212)
    - Fortune, "The $400 Million Friendship," April 9, 1990 (Box 212)
    - Institutional Investor"Al Taubman on the prowl," December 1986, .ZIP file
    - Jewish News"Lunch With A Legend," 2005, .JPG file
    - Lawyers Title News"Taubman Sees More Work in U.S. Shopping Center Development," September-October 1973, .ZIP file
    - Men's Wear"Retail: Selling Only the Best," April 11, 1983, .ZIP file
    - Michigan Daily"Medical School receives $56-million gift from Taubman," April 21, 2011, .ZIP file
    - Michigan Difference"A. Alfred Taubman: The Vision, the Legacy," Spring 2011, .ZIP file
    - Michigan Magazine, "Michiganian of the Year," January 8, 1984 (Box 212)
    - National Enquirer Lawsuit (Box 212)
    - New York Times, "Taubman: Systematic Acquirer," March 10, 1986 (Box 212)
    - News clipping, "Cancer center dedicates addition,"1982, .ZIP file
    - Oakland Press, "Al Taubman Gambles on a $2 Billion Deal," September 19, 1985 (Box 212)
    - Riverfront Groundbreaking Articles 1982 (Box 212)
    - Shopping Center Business, "Taubman's 50-Year Legacy," October 1999, .ZIP file (Box 212)
    - Spy Magazine Article and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 212)
    - Tattler [Tatler?], "Gone to the Man with the Blonde on His Arm," 1993, .ZIP file
    - University of Michigan Philanthropy Network"15 Minutes with Alfred Taubman, University Citizen," January 19, 2011, .MHT file
    - The University Record, "Taubman hopes students will experience 'wonderment'," October 18, 1999, .ZIP file
    - Veja Magazine, 1985 (Box 212)
    - Visual Merchandising, "Non-selling 'People' Space Draws Crowds," October 1975, .ZIP file
    - Washington Business, "Taubman Sets Stable Course for Woodies," January 21, 1985 (Box 212)
    - Washington Post, 1992 (Box 212)
    - W Magazine, April 2007, .ZIP file
  - Correspondence
    - 1964-1968, 19 folders (Box 213)
    - 1969-1970, 9 folders (Box 214)
    - 1980-1982, 25 folders (Box 215)
    - 1983-1984, 29 folders (Box 216)
    - 1985, 15 folders (Box 217)
    - 1985-1988, 16 folders (Box 218)
    - 1989-1991, 6 folders (Box 219)
    - 2000-2002, 23 folders (Box 220)
      (includes testimonial letters, 2001)
    - 2002-2003, 16 folders (Box 221)
  - Plaques
    - 1960 Allied Jewish Campaign -- Outstanding Service (Box 222)
    - 1962 Brandeis University Salutes A. Alfred Taubman and Names Him a Fellow of the University (Box 222)
    - 1965 United Jewish Appeal (20th anniversary of V-E Day) (Box 222)
    - 1966 Allied Jewish Campaign-Distinguished Leadership Plaque (Box 222)
    - 1976 Detroit Area Council (Box 222)
    - 1983 In Commemoration of the USFL Inaugural Season (Box 222)
    - 1992 Michigan Special Olympics, Snowmobile Endurance Riders (Box 222)
    - 1999 In Appreciation Tucson Accelerated High School (Box 222)
    - Undated Ferndale Fire Department -- "Fire Safety House", citation under glass (Box 222)
  - Awards, Certificates, and Drawings
    - Brandeis University (Brandeis University Clubs) 1960 (Box 223)
    - Ferris State University 2000 (Box 223)
    - Ohio State University (Canfield Society) 1997 (Box 223)
    - Congregation Shaarey Zedek (Grateful Recognition --115th Anniversary) 1976 (Box 223)
    - Lakeside Center, Certificate of Appreciation 1976 (Box 223)
    - Youth Development Corp. 1998 (Box 223)
    - Appointment to Membership in Governor's Council 1976 (Box 223)
    - Wayne County Executive Task Force on Infant Mortality 1993 (Box 223)
    - Associated General Contractors of America (Philip Taubman Memoriam) (Box 223)
    - Poem "A-L-F-R-E-D Wishing You Continued Success" from Harry Thomas (Box 223)
    - Framed Drawing by Williams (?) (Box 223)
    - Royal Academy of Arts Watercolor, from Hugh Casson (Text fading) (Box 223)
    - The Fund for America's Future 1986 (Box 224)
  - Photographs
    - Black and white photograph of dining room of Cadillac House Motel undated (Box 224)
    - Colored photograph of sail boat on Detroit River (Box 224)
    - Colored photographs of American States Insurance Co. building undated (Box 224)
    - Chicago Symphony Orchestra Concert at Woodfield 1974 (Box 224)
    - Colored photograph of car in front on home (Box 224)
    - Photographs of interior of home (photographed by Balthazar Korab) (Box 224)
    - Double-sided mounted photograph, one side is colored image of the interior of a home (probably by B. Korab); the reverse side is of an unidentified building, perhaps a school (Box 224)
  - Digital Images and Video Recordings
    The bulk of the digital content (23.9 GB) is contained in the Digital Images and Video Recordings subseries, which is divided into four subgroups: "Family and Personal," "Taubman Centers," "Interviews, Philanthropic Activities, Biographical programs, etc.," and "Topical and Miscellaneous." The "Family and Personal" materials consist primarily of images and videos related to the Taubman family, including A. Alfred Taubman's parents, children, and grandchildren, but also includes school photographs and a video made to celebrate his 60th birthday in 1984. The "Taubman Centers" materials include a "Taubman Unplugged" program for employees where A. Alfred Taubman answers questions about his life and work after publishing Threshold Resistance in 2007, a Town Hall meeting in 2009, and an interview conducted with Taubman to celebrate the 60th anniversary of the company in 2010. The remaining materials in this subseries primarily document various aspects of A. Alfred Taubman's life and work, particularly related to his philanthropic and civic activities. Materials presented under "Interviews, Philanthropic Activities, Biographical programs, etc." are arranged chronologically and represent individual events or programs, whereas materials presented under "Topical and Miscellaneous" are arranged by subject. Several videos and sets of images in both subgroups relate to the University of Michigan, particularly the University Health System and Replacement Hospital Project. Philanthropic and civic activities involving other universities and causes, as well as various trips and recreational activities are also represented. Other videos and images relate to Taubman's life and work as a whole, including several connected to the release of his book, Threshold Resistance in 2007
    - Family and Personal
      - A. Alfred Taubman school photographs 1942, 1948, .ZIP file
      - Alfred Taubman's Home Movies, circa 1950s, .MP4 file
      - Gayle Taubman Kalisman (daughter) family photographs 1951-2009, .ZIP file
      - Happy Birthday 1984, .MP4 file
      - Jason Interviews His Grandfather on Philanthropy 2008, .MP4 file
      - Jeff Miro: Taubman foundations and four points of focus 2008, .MP4 files
      - Philip and Fannie Taubman (parents) family photographs, circa 1940s, undated, .ZIP file
      - Robert S. Taubman (son) family photographs 1967-2009, .ZIP file
      - Sam Taubman (brother) photographs 1942-2004, .ZIP file
      - Taubman Family Gathering Booklet 2010, .ZIP file
      - The Taubman Family Field Trip 'Where It All Started' 2010, .MP4 files
      - Visiting previous homes 2010, .MOV file
      - William S. Taubman (son) and family 1958-2006, .ZIP file
    - Taubman Centers
      - Taubman Unplugged [with Chris Tennyson] April 2007, .MP4 files
      - Town Hall Meeting February 17, 2009, .MP4 files
      - Taubman Interview for 60th Anniversary 2010, .MP4 files
    - Interviews, Philanthropic Activities, Biographical programs, etc. (arranged chronologically)
      - Jewish Community Campus dedication July 22, 1997, .ZIP file
      - Celebration of Friendship luncheon, celebrating the friendship of Max M. Fisher, Damon J. Keith, and A. Alfred Taubman July 23, 2003, .ZIP file
      - ULI (Urban Land Institute) Lifetime Achievement Award Presentation 2005
        - Video, .MP4 file
        - Remarks and images, .ZIP file
      - A. Alfred Taubman, A Video Portrait, circa 2005, .MP4 files
      - A. Alfred Taubman Portraits 2006, .ZIP file
      - Function is Beauty/Inside the Mind of A. Alfred Taubman 2006, .MP4 file
      - Interview with A. Alfred Taubman 2006, .MP4 files
      - RHP [Replacement Hospital Project] 20th Anniversary
        - Photo presentation, RHP 20th Anniversary Celebration July 11, 2006, .MP4 file
        - 20th Anniversary Celebration Photos and Historical Images 2006, .ZIP file
        - Historical images and key people 2006, .ZIP file
      - Museum of Arts and Design Visionaries November 2006, .ZIP file
      - Cityscape Detroit, "Taubman Unplugged," December 2006, .ZIP file
      - A Portrait of Giving: Portrait Unveiling 2007, .MP4 files
      - A. Alfred Taubman Remarks for Manoogian Wing Opening (Detroit Institute of Arts) 2007, .MP4 file
      - Taubman Television, CBS News Sunday Morning and Charlie Rose 2007, .MP4 files
      - CNBC "High Net Worth," May 6, 2007, .ZIP file
      - Charlie Rose episode with Taubman interview August 29, 2007, .MP4 file
      - Bill Clinton/Cure MI Event for Proposal 2 October 9, 2008, .MP4 file
      - CNBC "American Greed" on Sotheby's antitrust case 2008, .MP4 file
      - Symposium of the Alfred Taubman Institute October 7, 2008, .WMV and .MP4 files
      - A. Alfred Taubman Tribute Photo Montage November 14, 2009, .MP4 files
      - Henry Ford program, On Innovation images June 2009, .ZIP file
      - Detroit Economic Club event December 9, 2009, .ZIP file
      - Lawrence Tech: A. Alfred Taubman: Entrepreneur, Pioneer, Philanthropist, circa 2010, .MP4 files
      - A. Alfred Taubman: Transforming Medicine, Transforming Lives 2011, .MP4 file
      - University of Michigan Donation Signing Ceremony March 16, 2011, .MP4 files
      - Harvard University visit, A. Alfred Taubman, Abigail and Les Wexner April 13, 2011, .ZIP file
      - University of Michigan Regents' Meeting and Biomedical Science Research Building Naming Celebration April 21, 2011, .MP4 files
      - University of Michigan Celebration of Taubman gift 2011, .ZIP file
      - Wharton/Peter Linneman Retirement April 27, 2011, .MP4 file
      - Lawrence Tech Winterlude 2012, .ZIP file
      - Interview about embracing aging by Keith Famie 2012, .ZIP file
      - Exhibit, 'Pioneering the Purchase: A Retrospective Exhibition Honoring A. Alfred Taubman,' 2012, .ZIP file
      - Taubman Prize for Excellence in Translational Medical Science October 11, 2012, .MP4 file
      - Goodfellows Breakfast October 19, 2012, .ZIP file
      - "A Visit to Sotheby's," circa 2014, . MP4 and .ZIP files
      - "A. Alfred Taubman: A Man and His Art" undated
        - Teaser Clip, .MP4 files
        - Bloomfield Hills, .MP4 files
        - New York, .MP4 files
        - Palm Beach, .MP4 files
        - Southampton, .MP4 files
    - Topical and Miscellaneous
      - Awards and news articles 2008-2011, .ZIP file
      - Brown University
        - Images 1985, 2005, .ZIP file
        - Portrait 2005, .ZIP file
      - Caricatures 1979-1995, .ZIP file
      - College for Creative Studies [CCS] in Detroit 2009, .ZIP file
      - Detroit Institute of Arts [DIA] 2007, 2009, .ZIP file
      - Education 1980s, 1997, .ZIP file
      - Fisher-Taubman Community Center in Israel, circa 1983, .ZIP file
      - Fisher-Taubman Garden at Liberty Bell Park in Jerusalem 1979-2008, .ZIP file
      - Fishing 1980-2012, .ZIP file
      - Golf 1967-2005, .ZIP file
      - Harvard University Kennedy School of Government 1986-2012, .ZIP file
      - Honorary degrees 1985-2000, .ZIP files
      - Israel trip 2007, .ZIP file
      - Keith, Damon 1994-2010, undated, .ZIP file
      - Lawrence Technological University, .ZIP file
        - Honorary Degree 1984
        - Student Services Center groundbreaking and opening 2005, 2006
        - Beverly Pepper Sculpture dedication 2009
        - Teaching 2010
        - Fisher Award 2011
      - Levin, Carl 1992, .ZIP file
      - Mixed photographs 1942-2011, .ZIP file
      - Overseas trips 1973-1994, .ZIP file
      - Reading Works 2012, .ZIP file
      - Shoots 2004-2012, .ZIP file
      - Steeplechase 1984, .ZIP file
      - Threshold of Resistance promotional images and events, 2007, .ZIP file
      - University of Michigan
        - College of Architecture 1999-2011, .ZIP file
        - Medical Library 2006, 2009, .ZIP file
        - Medical Research Institute 2008-2011, .ZIP file
        - Replacement Hospital 1981, 1983, 2006, .ZIP file
        - Miscellaneous events 1991, 2008-2011, .ZIP files
          - Honorary Doctorate May 4, 1991
          - Dr. Kim Eagle 2005
          - MichiganCures event with Bill Clinton October 10, 2008
          - Philip J. Bowen Award 2009
          - Legacy Night Gala honoring A. Alfred Taubman June 9, 2011
          - Young People of the Taubman Institute Inaugural Event at Sotheby's June 13, 2011
      - Urban Land Institute (ULI) Russian Delegation images 1985, .ZIP file
      - Various articles, documents, etc. 1977-2012, .ZIP file
  - Analog Video Recordings
    - VHS
      - Rich Fisher-Straight Talk, undated (Box 225)
      - The Taubman Company, Inc. "AAT," undated (Box 225)
      - Alfred Taubman, Money Program 04/03/2002 (Box 225)
      - Alfred Taubman, The Investigators, Court TV National 05/06/2004 (Box 225)
      - Sotheby's Good Morning America/ABC National 04/03/2002 (Box 225)
    - Beta/Misc
      - Alfred Taubman, Happy 60th Birthday 1984 (Box 225)
      - Alfred Taubman, Interview 05/16/2006 (Box 225)
- Athena Azerbaijan and Russia Development Projects 1995-2002
  The Athena Azerbaijan and Russia Development Projects series- documents the Athena Group's financing, design, construction, and leasing of retail, office, warehouse, and mixed-use sites in Moscow and Baku, Azerbaijan. Materials include correspondence and memoranda, investment prospectuses and investor updates, progress reports, architectural drawings, legal and financial agreements, and photographs of construction activities. The files include documents addressed to Taubman and Avner Naggar at The Taubman Company, as well as copies of documents created or received by Louis Dubin, Metin Negrin, Bob Rylee, and other members of the Athena Group's management.
  - Landmark Building (Baku, Azerbaijan)
    - Correspondence 1996-1997, 17 folders (Box 226)
    - Baku memos (Box 226)
    - Landmark Building, Baku (Box 226)
    - Landmark Building and ST Group (Box 226)
    - Landmark Building, photographs of renovation (Box 226)
      (includes photographs of other buildings)
    - Floor plans and elevations (Box 226)
    - Plan details (Box 226)
    - Ekpar Industries, pre-qualification documents for renovation project (Box 226)
    - Hillman Dibernardo (lighting designer) (Box 226)
    - Baku service providers (Box 226)
    - Baku competitive projects (Box 226)
    - Baku Tombstone (Box 226)
    - Landmark Building, Metin Negrin's files 1996-1997, 2000, 2 folders (Box 227)
    - Landmark Building preliminary due diligence report (Box 227)
    - Baku II (Box 227)
    - Hyatt Hotels new project (Box 227)
    - Azerbaijan Hotel renovation (Box 227)
    - Execution copies
      - Development fee agreement (Box 227)
      - Additional financing (Box 227)
      - Option agreement (Box 227)
      - Consent (Box 227)
      - Stock purchase (Box 227)
      - Distribution agreement (Box 227)
    - Triton Joint Venture Corp, articles of incorporation (Box 227)
    - Neptune Joint Venture (Box 227)
    - Neptune Financial Information (Box 227)
    - Baku, Neptune (Box 227)
    - Baku Wire Instructions (Box 227)
    - Baku Investors, LLC, 4 folders (Box 227)
    - Baku Investor updates (Box 227)
    - Transfer of shares to Baku Investors (Box 227)
    - Hazar Investments, Ltd. (Box 227)
    - Zirkin-Cutler Investments (investment counsel to Athena Group) (Box 227)
    - Global Securities Inc., Azerbaijan Real Estate Fund (Box 227)
    - Harvard Capital Management (Box 227)
    - Republic National Bank (Box 227)
    - Baku general ledger and invoices (Box 227)
    - Nikolai Worp (leading agent?) (Box 228)
    - Jane Gordon, Director of Leasing (Box 228)
    - American companies operating in Azerbaijan (Box 228)
    - Lease agreements, various, 3 folders (Box 228)
    - Arthur Anderson lease agreement (Box 228)
    - Electrolux lease agreement (Box 228)
    - Emerson lease agreement (Box 228)
    - Exxon lease agreements and correspondence, 3 folders (Box 228)
    - KPMG lease agreement (Box 228)
    - Azerbaijan map (Box 228)
    - Baku drawings, photographs (Box 228)
    - Baku II plans (Box 228)
  - Arbat Center
    - Arbat Center documents (includes current contracts, new contracts, planned contracts, and contractor agreements) 1998 (Box 229)
      (documents in Russian)
    - L.P. Pomplemousse (Cambridge Associates) (Box 229)
    - Price Waterhouse, 2 folders (Box 229)
    - Akin Gump (Republic Bank) (Box 229)
    - Miro Weiner & Kramer (Box 229)
    - SunAmerica (and Eli Broad) (Box 229)
    - Taubman (Box 229)
    - Republic Bank (Box 229)
    - Ellerbee Becket, architectural (Box 229)
    - Market Study (Box 229)
    - Monte Cristo, Nicholas Berggruen (Box 229)
    - Design issues (Box 229)
    - Documentation (Box 229)
    - Finance (Box 229)
    - Cash flows (Box 229)
    - Soft costs (Box 229)
    - Hard costs (Box 229)
    - Drawings (Box 229)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 229)
    - Arbat, 2 folders (Box 229)
    - Updates September 18, 1998 (Box 229)
    - Skanska downpayment (Box 229)
    - Payment reconciliation August 1998 (Box 229)
    - Nat West account (Box 229)
    - Due diligence (Box 229)
    - Arbat slide presentation (Box 229)
    - Photographs (Box 230)
    - Investment summary (Box 230)
    - Legal (Box 230)
    - Plans and drawings, 2 folders (Box 230)
    - Correspondence (Box 230)
    - Construction plans and agreements (Box 231)
    - Draft agreements (Box 231)
    - Exhibits to LLC agreement (Box 231)
    - Investor letters (Box 231)
    - Arbat/Alfa (Box 231)
    - Alfa Development (Box 231)
    - Alfa costs, contracts, etc. (Box 231)
    - AOZT Syracuse/Alfa (Box 231)
    - Joint venture, 2 folders (Box 231)
    - Courdet Brothers (Box 231)
    - Rosenman and Colin/Joe Getraer (Box 231)
    - Steptoe and Johnson (Box 231)
    - Cooper and Lybrand (Box 231)
    - Tax structure, general (Box 231)
    - Financials/budgets (Box 231)
    - Certificate of formation/Athena Arbat I and II (Box 231)
    - General correspondence (Box 232)
    - Athena/Arbat Finances (Box 232)
    - Arbat documents (old drafts) (Box 232)
    - Internal notes/correspondence (Box 232)
    - Pre-closing archives (Box 232)
    - Agreements (Box 232)
  - Balchug Plaza
    - Project drawings, 5 folders (Box 233)
    - Balchug Udine meeting May 25, 1998 (Box 233)
    - ST Balchug correspondence (Box 233)
    - Balchug (Cyprus) documents (Box 233)
    - Investor letters (Box 233)
    - Balchug (includes mechanical specifications and financial information) (Box 233)
    - Financial (Box 233)
    - ST Balchug closing checklist documents (Box 233)
    - Balchug (Cyprus) Athena loan agreement (Box 233)
    - Leasing (Box 233)
    - VAV vs Fan Coil (Box 233)
    - Project schedule (Box 233)
    - Contract BPL01/98 (Box 233)
    - Republic lease proposal (Box 233)
    - Balchug Plaza project (Box 233)